euttaranchal.com 2018-12-05

# eUttaranchal - Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policies laid down below are general and applicable throughout the website http://www.euttaranchal.com

To read the specific _**[Privacy Policies for our Matrimonial Service](http://www.euttaranchal.com/matrimonials/register/privacy-policy.php)**_ , please [click here](http://www.euttaranchal.com/matrimonials/register/privacy-policy.php)

**Information Collection and Use**

  * eUttaranchal collects personal information when you register with eUttaranchal or its network partners, when you use eUttaranchal services, when you visit eUttaranchal pages and when you enter promotions. eUttaranchal may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address and information about your assets. Once you register with eUttaranchal and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * eUttaranchal automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, eUttaranchal cookie information, and the page you request. 
  * eUttaranchal uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

###  Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * eUttaranchal does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * eUttaranchal has partnered with trusted agents and parties for various services. Your personal details may be shared with our trusted partners who may contact you to provide products or services you've requested at eUttaranchal. 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of eUttaranchal’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if eUttaranchal is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, eUttaranchal! will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * eUttaranchal displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria.
  * eUttaranchal does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

### Cookies

  * eUttaranchal may set and access cookies on your computer. 
  * eUttaranchal lets other companies/advertisers that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to eUttaranchal's cookies. 

### Your Account Information and Preferences

**General**

  * You can edit your eUttaranchal Account Information at any time. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the eUttaranchal service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Newsletter, that are considered part of your eUttaranchal account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * eUttaranchal may update this policy at any time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your eUttaranchal account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

This website (http://www.euttaranchal.com) is the owned and operated by **DeeBee Web Services Pvt Ltd**. 

Should you have further queries about our privacy policy, please contact our support team at [care@eutn.in](mailto:care@eutn.in)
